[♪ opening theme song playing]
[Ivan chuckles]
None of these people had to die
if Yuru had come alone
like I told him to.
And these must
be the Divine Guardians.
Yuru's daemons.
What I don't get is
why the natural enemies
of Break and Seal would form
a contract with the twin.
Especially you, Left.
Your compatibility
with Seal couldn't be worse.
With you around,
Seal might flat out refuse
to form a contract with Yuru.
Hate to say it, but...
to ensure everything works out,
you gotta die.
[Right grunts]
The gentleman wants a duel!
What say you?
[LEFT] I gladly accept.
Interesting.
From what I have observed,
swordsmen are a rarity
in these modern streets.
Four centuries ago,
they darkened every doorway.
I should warn you that
there's more to these swords
than one might guess.
Naturally.
That's why
I'll snap them in two.
[Left scoffs]
[Ivan exclaims softly]
[LEFT] Uh?
[Left grunts]
[Dera grunts]
[DERA] Left, you're hurt!
[LEFT] Calm yourself.
You shall take me to the
home improvement merchant later.
Yeah, sure, of course.
Because...
To fix this.
They peddle adhesives made
for stone, yes?
Hold up. That would heal you?
You forget that we are statues.
This will take some time
to repair,
but losing an arm or two
shan't be the death of me.
[DERA] So reckless.
Isn't that a pain in the ass?
What is it going to take
to kill you?
It is you who are the pain!
Those swords are sharp
and can regenerate.
[sniffing]
Observe, Left.
His katanas.
Do you smell it?
They reek of blood.
How are you surprised?
He's surrounded by corpses.
Mm?
[grunts]
If my nose is to be believed,
you've murdered an unbelievable
number of people.
Well, a man's gotta
earn a living somehow.
I'll slice up anyone
for a check.
Human or daemon, doesn't matter.
Whatever the job requires of me.
[Right sniffing]
I smell something else on you.
There's a relatively fresh blood
and blood from Higashi Village.
But beneath that,
a whisper of something else.
A scent the two of us
are familiar with.
It's Yuru's kin!
I smell the blood
of Mine and Nagisa!
[ASUMA]
So what do you say, Yuru?
Tell me, would it
please you to die?
Why? Do you intend to kill me?
I would be extremely grateful
if you made the choice for me.
It'd save me a lot of trouble.
Did the head of the Kagemoris
order this?
[ASUMA] No. My thinking
doesn't align with my father's.
The main Kagemori clan
is way too soft to be effective.
Oh, right, allow me
to introduce Shingo.
He's my mother's older brother.
[Shingo grunts]
You know, there's no place
for you in Higashi anymore.
[Yuru breathes shakily]
Your family got outta there
years ago.
And what did that get them?
The villagers you loved so much
tracked your sister down
and killed her.
They've even tried to murder you
on a few occasions.
You don't owe these people
a thing.
It's time to leave them behind.
[scoffs]
Instead, you can join
the Shingo clan.
We could treat you very well.
You mean the clan
that wants me dead?
That went into the village
and kidnapped some kids
who must be terrified?
We needed hostages,
or else you wouldn't have
cooperated!
Don't worry, the fake Asa
and the kid are in a safe place
under watchful eyes, unharmed.
They're just
on a little vacation.
And yeah, of course
I would like it
if you kicked the bucket.
Seeing your corpse
would make my day.
Perhaps phrase that differently?
But I'm gonna need you
to accept your death. Cool?
What's cool about that?
[SHINGO] By the way,
you know the shaman, right?
Mountain of a man?
What? You mean Yama?
He comes
to the village sometimes
to heal the sick.
If you're wondering who sent
the bandits to assassinate you,
it was him.
[Yuru gasps]
[SHINGO] Tadera...
The guy who's supposed to be
looking out for you?
He hung out with the shaman
all the time.
You can't trust him, either.
Higashi Village kept
Seal a secret
and waited for their chance
to kill you.
If they'd had it their way,
you would have snuffed it
years ago.
Don't give those fanatics
another spare thought.
Instead, choose
to give up your own life.
Let that damn village
crumble and die.
[Yuru breathes shakily]
[ASUMA] Please, Uncle,
I know how passionate you are,
but you shouldn't say
such things.
Everything in this world
serves some purpose.
[Yuru exhales]
[YURU] "A child like you
isn't needed in this world."
[ASUMA] Yes. The village
that produces Break and Seal
should be allowed to live on.
We mustn't reject their
very existence.
That's weird.
You don't agree with your uncle?
How does that work
if you're on the same side?
[ASUMA] Like Higashi Village
and the Kagemoris,
there are
a number of differing opinions
represented
within the Shingo Clan.
That's a positive thing.
It would be dangerous
for us to be
in total agreement
with one another.
What the Shingo clan
is united on
is the idea that
those who wield special powers
should be able to use them
without restraint.
So long as they're overseen
by a responsible party.
There are plenty of perks
to joining us.
The kind of support we can offer
will change your life.
I'm talking money, resources.
Anything you might want.
[YURU] I already made my wishes
clear at the Kagemori mansion.
The only thing I want
is a normal life.
I want to hunt, farm,
cook over charcoal.
Nothing special.
[Yozakura groans softly]
[YURU] I want to find
Mother and Father, too.
Then...
there's Asa.
I don't know if she realizes
she's in a prison,
but I want to free her from it.
And one day soon,
we'll all live an ordinary life
full of laughter together.
[RIGHT] Admit it. You murdered
Yuru's parents, didn't you?
And if you're not to blame,
whoever was the master
of those sword daemons
before you spilled their blood.
I can smell Mine and Nagisa
on those blades.
[Dera grunts]
[Ivan chuckles]
Who knows? I've cut down
so many people,
I can't remember them all.
Don't dodge the question.
[IVAN] Let's see what the swords
have to say.
-Dera, leave us and find Yuru.
-Uh?
[RIGHT] We'll take this man
and his daemons alive.
[LEFT] A gift for our master.
[DERA] You got it.
Fool. Wasting shots.
[DERA] I'm out!
See you later, sword pervert!
[IVAN] That bastard!
He tricked me
into looking at the lights
right before he killed them.
My eyes aren't going to adjust
any time soon.
Let me guess,
Left and Right
use their sense of smell
to navigate the darkness.
Ugh. How annoying.
[loud crash]
[DERA] Genius plan.
I said I'd look for Yuru,
but I have no idea
where to start.
Is he even in this warehouse
district anymore?
Uh?
Wait, Tadera?
Yeah. And you're a bandit.
-You hurt?
-I'll live,
but the rest of my crew
wasn't so lucky.
Did you meet the guy
with daemon swords?
[DERA] Yeah, I did.
Looked like bad news.
What the heck are you
even doing here, Tadera?
We made sure
that you wouldn't know
anything about this job.
I bet that gravedigger
couldn't keep her mouth shut!
Who? You mean Hana?
She's a steel trap.
One of your bandits
has been leaking info to me
on the side for a while now.
Didn't make it outta
that warehouse, though.
Ah, damn it. You just can't rely
on anyone these days.
[DERA] Dead men tell no tales.
Yuru came to rescue the fake Asa
and the kid from the village,
but got taken by a daemon
that looked like a crow.
[BANDIT] He's been kidnapped?
Are you an idiot?
Why would you bring him here?
Seems like just about
everybody wants the twins dead.
And Yuru, that kid's desperate
to find something he can trust.
He figured out you bandits
were trying to assassinate him.
You can imagine
how he took that.
Hey. You were
on our side first, Tadera.
Did you forget?
Don't start pretending
-you care about that boy.
-[DERA] Yeah, good point.
I've been keeping secrets
from him, too.
I don't expect Yuru
to fully trust me.
He's got no reason to.
The thing is, we've bonded.
In the past, I could ignore
some parts of my job.
But lately, it seems I've had
a change of heart.
So you're betraying
Higashi Village?
I'm not betraying anybody.
If you promise to back off
and leave Yuru alone,
I'll have no reason
to fight with you.
They're the first twins
in 400 years.
If they had their hands
on Break and Seal,
Higashi Village could conquer
the entire world with ease.
[Dera grunts]
I don't want to end up
an old man
thinking about
how I got ahead in my life
by sacrificing two
innocent children. Understand?
[bandit grunts]
[breathes uneasily]
[sighs]
We can argue about this later.
Let's look for Yuru.
[Dera grunts]
After I saw the message
about this warehouse,
I did some digging
to see who owned it.
Find anything?
[BANDIT]
It belongs to TT Logistics.
Their parent company
is Shingo Shipping.
There's a Shingo clan
that's related to the Kagemoris.
You know Gonzo's second kid,
Asuma?
They're his family
on the mom's side.
I looked into every business
I could find
connected to the Shingos.
TT Logistics,
Kibushi Industries.
Plenty more.
[DERA] Whoa,
that's one hell of a list.
Are we gonna have to search
all of them?
No way. If Yuru was kidnapped
by a daemon,
my guess is it'll still be
standing guard over him.
We'll hunt daemons with daemons.
[both exclaim]
[BANDIT] These are mine,
Mamegarasu.
[BOW-LEGS] I'm Bow-Legs.
[PIGEON-TOES] I'm Pigeon-Toes.
Hi, good to meet you.
[BANDIT] I want you to help us
locate any daemons nearby.
[BOTH] Happy to be of service.
[BANDIT] You don't have
any daemons of your own?
Nah, I'm pretty useless
on that front.
[BANDIT] If you can see them,
then you must've had
some in the past.
So what's the issue?
You're not going to form
a contract with a new pair?
[BOTH] So sad!
[Dera sighs]
Well, maybe one day,
if I get the chance.
♪
[clanging]
[sword swooshing]
[Right grunting]
[Ivan sighs]
[IVAN] I'm finally adjusting
to the dark.
[SHOKYO]
Quit wasting time, monkey.
They're making this harder
than it needs to be
by trying to capture me alive.
Their attacks
would be easier to read
if they were actually going
for the kill.
I only remember throwing down
the gauntlet to Left!
Turning this into
a two versus one
hardly seems fair!
You'll make your master cry
acting like this.
Where's your honor?
Your humanity?
[RIGHT] We're not humans.
[LEFT] And Yuru won't mind.
[Ivan grunts]
[IVAN] These brutes.
I'd like to take this outside,
but with them blocking
either exit,
that'll be a trial of its own.
They want me with
limited space to move.
Ah, crap. Shouldn't have left
these bodies lying around.
They're tripping hazards
in the dark.
Why don't we take this outside?
You should treat the dead
with a bit more care.
[Ivan exclaims]
[IVAN]
Look at that beautiful moon.
Unless our master
should spare you,
this full moon may be your last.
Savor it.
Well said.
I hope you take your own words
to heart.
[Left gasps]
[RIGHT] Left, watch out!
[grunts]
You had my back. Thank you.
You're damn right I did.
If your goal's "defeat Left,"
you'd best be ready
to get through me first.
Is that the case?
Fine!
[Right grunting]
I suppose that's what they call
losing the battle
to win the war?
[Right grunting]
[RIGHT] He's evading our attacks
by a hair's breadth!
[LEFT] He's learned
our ranges perfectly.
[Right grunts]
[IVAN] A left hook.
With her reach,
a half step back
will be enough to dodge.
Then I'll counter
by taking her other arm.
What kind of madwoman would use
her own severed arm as a weapon?
[Ivan sighs]
This is starting
to get too much for me. [spits]
[Shokyo scoffs]
Weak flesh bag! Push yourself!
[IVAN] Need I remind you
my right leg is wounded
from where you stabbed it,
Shokyo?
[SHOKYO] You monkeys
should regenerate faster!
-[DAIKYO] Ivan.
-Whoa, you spoke up?
What's the occasion, Daikyo?
[DAIKYO] Something has arrived.
[IVAN] Hmm?
[DAIKYO]
Something really bad is here.
[MAN 1]
You should have been there.
[chuckles]
[MAN 2] No way that's real.
[MAN 1] I swear, I'm serious.
Think I'd lie?
[GONZO] Hello.
[BOTH] Mm?
Quick question, gentlemen.
Is this the office
of Shingo Shipping,
by any chance?
[BOTH] Afraid not!
Sorry, but we're
Kibushi Industries.
[line ringing]
[GONZO] Ah, but isn't that
a Shingo subsidiary?
[MAN 1] I wouldn't know.
I'm just a part-timer.
I don't keep up
with that corporate stuff.
-[Gonzo laughs]
-[MAN 2] Hey.
-Send some guys.
-[GONZO] Don't play dumb.
[MAN 2] Looks like
Gonzo Kagemori's...
[GONZO] Go on.
[whimpers]
[GONZO] I didn't mean
to interrupt your call.
[squeaking]
Send your friends over!
I'll take on
every last one of you.
[both trembling]
[BANDIT]
What's wrong, little guys?
Why'd they start trembling
out of the blue?
[Dera gasps]
[both trembling]
[DERA] Seems like
something real nasty
just showed up.
[grunting]
[MAN] Who is this old man?
Get away! Gramps here
is a Daemon Wielder!
Oh, Hebota!
I am seriously glad
to see you, man!
You guys don't stand a chance
against him.
You wanna fight daemons?
Then you're gonna need
some daemons of your own.
Now go, my...
[gasps]
-[screams]
-[BOTH] No, Hebota!
Wait, what?
I can't tell what's going on.
Anyone here with daemons,
team up to take down Grandpa.
[MAN 1] Great.
How can we do that?
[growling]
[MAN 2] The geezer's got
more pairs of ‘em
than I can count!
[all screaming]
[rumbling]
[humming]
Hmm. That is a lot of noise.
Wonder...
[screams]
[Gonzo grunting]
[GUARD] Some random old dude
is out there shadow boxing.
And every time he swings,
something explodes.
♪
Hello, headquarters?
I seem to be hallucinating.
Can I have a break?
[MALE HQ] What?
Quit screwing around
and get back to work.
[guard cries] I hate this job!
[rumbling]
[footsteps]
[DERA] What? Is that the head
of the Kagemori clan?
You mean Gonzo's here?
Of course my guys
are freaked out!
They're sensing
a mansion's worth of daemons.
Who wouldn't be?
Awesome. How are we
supposed to find Yuru now?
♪
[RIGHT] Huh?
What are we sensing?
-[IVAN] Hmm.
-If I did not know better,
I'd say the Kagemori manor
itself sprouted legs
and walked here.
[HAGURE] You've got it!
Just fill in all the spots
I marked with an X!
So, is this okay?
Perfect! Very precise.
You've got steady hands!
Now, where's
Miss "Zero Artistic Talent?"
You ask me, I'd say
you have a real knack for this!
Aw, I don't know about that.
Well, I'm gonna go take a bath,
so please just keep
doing what you're doing.
Aye, aye. [giggles]
[chuckles]
[door opens, closes]
[TACHIKAWA] Wait a sec,
how exactly did I get here?
How did a merc like me wind up
spot-filling for a mangaka?
[ASA] I want to see my brother.
What are you thinking, Asa?
Could you see yourself
being Hagure's assistant
for the rest of your life?
Or is there anything else
you want?
I want to see my brother.
Oh, right.
[phone vibrating]
-[TACHIKAWA] Hello?
-I want to see my brother.
Hold on, let me step outside
real quick.
It's a little noisy in here.
Yeah, I'm at work right now.
Yeah, everything
will be all right.
I figured out how we can deal
with all Mom's hospital bills.
Let your big sister handle it.
♪
Hey, Gabby, why don't we
take a break, also?
Right. Forgot.
She had a job to do.
Oh, wow, you're all by yourself.
Ms. Gabby's so protective,
she's normally stuck to you
like glue.
This is a rare sight, isn't it?
I suppose so.
You should be careful
not to let your guard down
when you're alone.
You never know when some more
assassins could sneak in here.
How about I stay
to keep you safe?
Hey, Akio?
You look strange.
Are you hiding something?
Akio?
Uh, no. I'm actually fine
by myself.
I said I'm okay. Hold on. Stop!
You'd better back up!
[breathes uneasily]
'Cause if you get closer...
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[GONZO] What a haul we've got!
[GABBY] Pretty sure
I made it crystal clear
when we first met
which one of us is stronger!
[AKIO] How unfortunate.
I hate it when women lie.